[{"answer": "Hey, could you do me a favour?  Could you shu", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I hate rental cars. Nothin' ever work", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Timed out perfectly. Drop off the car, pick up the rental car shuttle, we walk right on the plane... Oops", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hey! Wait up", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That's a pretty big tip..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "They don't get that much", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "They don't get that much", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "We can't ask him..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "*Fiv", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "We'll call him..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No time?  Is there time", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, have you ever flown first class", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Duty", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, I dunno how much duty is", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Duty is", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Duty is", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I like to stop at the duty free shop", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hey, I was gonna take that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't care when you got here, I want the magazine..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "There it is. Gate 46... We got plenty of time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How you gonna catch him? He's probably boarded the plane already", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How you gonna catch him? He's probably boarded the plane already", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "My credit card", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm not gonna give you my card unless you tell me what it's for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What, are you, nuts? You're gonna spend more on the ticket than you're gonna get back from that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What, are you, nuts? You're gonna spend more on the ticket than you're gonna get back from that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "This is a", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Excuse me? Excuse me, but I didn't get a meal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes, I'm sure! I would know if a tray of food had been served to me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I think it means when a Rabbi has inspected it, or something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "They don't eat pigs", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes, but you're still not allowed. These seats are very expensive", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You're going to have to go back to your seat", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Oh, no, please, don't send me back there. Please, I'll do anything. It's so nice up here. It's so comfortable up here. I don't want to go back there. Please don't send me back there...  Oh, you got", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Airport.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Ok, fine. I'll go back... You know, our goal should be a society", "qsentId": 38}]